<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Moments With You on TO CHHAYA, MY LOVE</title>
    <link>https://forchhaya.us/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Moments With You on TO CHHAYA, MY LOVE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://forchhaya.us/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>We decided to run for it and I&#39;m feeling excited by you</title>
      <link>https://forchhaya.us/post/beetlejuice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forchhaya.us/post/beetlejuice/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been an awful day and we almost decided not to get tickets. But we did get tickets. We ended up getting annoyed and we almost decided to not go to the play. But we did go to the play. We realized we were running late and almost decided to just walk and deal with it. But instead, you ran.
You ran, and I ran with you, and together we ran and ran and ran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> It’s the middle of an interview, and I keep messaging you. </title>
      <link>https://forchhaya.us/post/middle-of-an-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forchhaya.us/post/middle-of-an-interview/</guid>
      <description>It’s the middle of an interview, and I keep messaging you.
It’s nice, you know, to be able to share stuff. An Instagram reel of a cat overreaching, or bizarre things like a program requiring us to work ungodly hours. I want to immediately share with you. Or even nonsense because I want to see a notification saying ‘qt’ has messaged me back. It’s comfortable, like a being wrapped in a warm blanket while watching a movie at night, or listening to soft music as we drive into nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re on a run and I’m feeling in love with you.</title>
      <link>https://forchhaya.us/post/on-a-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forchhaya.us/post/on-a-run/</guid>
      <description>We’re on a run and I feel weightless.
Well, actually I’m in a lot of pain now, but just a few minutes ago, I felt like I could run forever. For as long as we had things to talk about, I could keep putting one step in front of another. And how could we not? Our favorite thing to do together is literally to do nothing, or anything together.
Now though, the miles are catching up, and I need to concentrate to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s a short drive and I’m feeling in love with you</title>
      <link>https://forchhaya.us/post/short-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forchhaya.us/post/short-drive/</guid>
      <description>It’s a short drive and I’m feeling in love with you The short drive home from the fourth coffee shop we visited hoping for a peaceful place to work before coming home at night is one of my favorite drives. Listening as you talk about a dress you tried on, or how many miles you managed to fit in during an OTF workout, or .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> You’ve fallen asleep on my arm and I’m feeling in love with you </title>
      <link>https://forchhaya.us/post/falling-asleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forchhaya.us/post/falling-asleep/</guid>
      <description>You’ve fallen asleep on my arm and I’m feeling in love with you Sometimes, in the comfort of thoughts formed half asleep, and get lost in thoughts haves and wants. Me? I want your quiet love. The love that’s there, and steady. The love of you falling asleep, curled into my chest, your body relaxing into mine. Your love, having remembered to set an alarm for a call early tomorrow, and mine, timing my breathing to match your movements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> We’re running around in a stone forest and I’m in a better mood when you’re around</title>
      <link>https://forchhaya.us/post/stone-hike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forchhaya.us/post/stone-hike/</guid>
      <description>We’re running around in a stone forest and I’m in a better mood when you’re around.
No seriously, I feel like half the time we’re just being, I have an ear to ear grin and I want to hug and squeeze you and go grocery shopping. But today, we’re dancing along to a Taekwondo song, galavanting through a hike, with the nature around us all etched stone. We’re racing around and exploring what we can see, being as loud as we are until we remember to be quiet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
